<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Yirggzmb's Stuff</title>
    <description>Yirggzmb's personal website, assorted video game and craft stuff</description>
    <link>https://yirggzmb.github.io/</link>
    <image>
      <url>https://yirggzmb.github.io/logo.png</url>
      <title>Yirggzmb's Stuff</title>
      <link>https://yirggzmb.github.io/</link>
    </image>
	
	<item>
	  <title>Critterpedia Field Journal</title>
	  <link>https://yirggzmb.github.io/animalcrossing/critterbook.html</link>
	  <description>Added a page for the Animal Crossing real world Critterpedia I created. This page features both photos of mine, as well as files and information about making one yourself. </description>
	  <pubDate>31 May 2025 06:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
	  <enclosure length="163840" type="image/jpg" url="https://yirggzmb.github.io/animalcrossing/images/critterbook/book-small.jpg" />
	</item>
	
	<item>
	  <title>Jack-o-Lantern Gallery</title>
	  <link>https://yirggzmb.github.io/miscart/pumpkins.html</link>
	  <description>Added a section for misc art and a gallery of Jack-o-Lanterns I've done over the years. </description>
	  <pubDate>06 Nov 2024 05:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
	  <enclosure length="150605" type="image/jpg" url="https://yirggzmb.github.io/miscart/images/pumpkins/2024-boththumb.jpg" />
	</item>
	
	<item>
	  <title>Tiny Life</title>
	  <link>https://yirggzmb.github.io/tinylife/index.html</link>
	  <description>Added a section for Tiny Life creations. </description>
	  <pubDate>02 Oct 2024 03:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
	  <enclosure length="305212" type="image/png" url="https://yirggzmb.github.io/tinylife/images/verdantshores/map.png" />
	</item>
	
	<item>
	  <title>Custom Designs - Wild World</title>
	  <link>https://yirggzmb.github.io/animalcrossing/WWCustomDesigns.html</link>
	  <description>Here are a selection of custom designs created in Wild World. The only way to get them is to recreate them yourself in game. These may also be useful in other games, however the color palettes there are different and you may have to tinker. Click on any image to see it larger. Each design will have, at minimum, a screenshot of the design in the designer with and without the grid. There will also likely be at least one image with the design using an alternative palette, so as to make the specific colors more clear which is used where. Where possible, I've also added screenshots or photos of the designs used in game, some in emulator and others photos of my actual DS.</description>
	  <pubDate>31 May 2024 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
	  <enclosure length="198580" type="image/png" url="https://yirggzmb.github.io/animalcrossing/images/designs/ww/BlueTiles.png" />
	</item>
	
	<item>
	  <title>Red Heart Granny all in one Square Yarn Experiment</title>
	  <link>https://yirggzmb.github.io/yarncrafts/GrannyAllInOneSquare.html</link>
	  <description>I'm fascinated by novelty yarns, especially the kind where it's something they're doing with color rather than texture. So while I knew going in that this "make a many color granny square without having to change yarns" idea was going to be a bit futzy, I was really curious JUST how annoying it would be. So here is a log of my attempt and general thoughts.</description>
	  <pubDate>28 May 2024 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
	  <enclosure length="195094" type="image/jp2" url="https://yirggzmb.github.io/yarncrafts/images/grannyallinone/001.jpg" />
	</item>
	
  </channel>
</rss>